‎NETFLIX アニメシリーズ
♪～
～♪
‎（デイビッド）
‎東からナイトシティに
The cargo's coming into
the city from the east.
‎移送されてくるブツを
‎街の外で車ごと頂く
We're taking the whole vehicle.
Haul's two 'n' a half mil.
‎報酬は250万
‎それを いつもの割合で山分けだ
Pot o' gold with the usual split.
‎（ファルコ）
‎俺のサイバーパンク歴でも
This one's definitely
the biggest job I've ever taken.
‎いちばん でかい仕事だ
‎（レベッカ）
‎フン まっ コーポ案件でしょ
Target's a corp, ain't it?
Three guesses which one it is.
‎盗む相手も察しがつくわ
‎（ファルコ）‎アラサカ… だな
Arasaka, of course.
Half a mil a head's nice 'n' all,
but I ain't even sure if it's worth it.
‎こりゃ50万でも割に合うか怪しいぜ
‎そもそも この人数でやる作戦か？
Really think five of us is enough?
Security footprint
on the convoy's peculiarly small.
‎（キーウィ）
‎運搬車以外は大した装備じゃないね
Arasaka's posted a limited crew to cast
a short shadow, keep a low profile.
‎アラサカは規模を絞って
‎シークレットに
‎輸送を行おうとしてるらしい
We'll strike the metal where it's soft.
‎それが今回の狙い目ってわけ
I dunno, man…
‎（レベッカ）‎ホントかよ～
Let's not overthink this.
‎（デイビッド）‎シンプルに考えよう
Smash, grab, deliver. It's what we do.
‎ターゲットから奪って
‎クライアントに渡す
Business as usual.
‎いつもどおりの仕事だ
‎（レベッカ）‎いつもどおりねえ
Business as usual my ass.
‎（ファラデー）
‎サイバースケルトンに
You think he'll withstand
the cyberskeleton?
‎耐えうる可能性だと？
‎（キーウィ）‎デイビッドの
‎サンデヴィスタンへの——
Arasaka does. After seeing his chemistry
mesh so well with the Sandevistan.
‎適応性を知って
‎アラサカが目をつけたのね
Tanaka wanted him back in the Academy
so he could test the cyberskeleton on him.
‎タナカはデイビッドを
‎アカデミーに呼び戻して
‎サイバースケルトンの実装テストを
‎するつもりだった
And this girl was trying to
bury that information
‎（ファラデー）‎この女
‎それを防ぐためにデータを破壊し
‎隠ぺい工作を行っていたわけか
so no one would come after him.
That's how I see it.
Frying Tanaka tied up a loose end.
‎（キーウィ）‎みたいね
‎タナカの脳もルーシーが焼いた
‎（ファラデー）‎フッ
‎メインやドリオは
‎巻き添えを食って死んだわけか
Maine and Dorio were just
collateral damage in her schemes.
That's one way of putting it…
‎（キーウィ）‎結果的にはね
So much carnage for one so petite.
‎（ファラデー）
‎かわいい顔をして恐ろしい女だな
How many did she kill just to save one?
‎自分の男を助けるために
‎何人殺した？
‎（ザバーッ！）
‎（キーウィ）
‎深く潜って分かったけど
Dove a little deeper and found that
she used to work for Arasaka.
‎この子 昔
‎アラサカに飼われてたみたい
They groomed her
to mine data in the Old Net.
‎オールドネットに送られる
‎兵隊として
‎（ベリッ！）
‎アラサカの‎ＩＣＥ(アイス)‎を突破したのも
‎うなずけるわ
Guess that's how she's been able to
get past Arasaka's ICE.
‎（ファラデー）
‎フハハハハハハッ いいぞ
This is perfect.
‎（ファラデー）
‎これは最高のサプライズだ
What a wonderful surprise.
We can dangle her in front of Arasaka.
‎これを材料にアラサカと交渉すれば
‎コーポの中枢に入るのも夢ではない
Our fast-lane ticket up
the corporate rungs!
Didn't see you as
such a simp corpo-climber.
‎（キーウィ）
‎それが あんたの目的だったわけ？
Is that really so strange?
‎（ファラデー）おかしいかね？
‎しょせんフィクサーなど
What are fixers
if not glorified pet owners
‎サイバーパンクにエサをやる
‎飼育員にすぎない
who keep their mercenary hounds well fed?
The only way to succeed in Night City
is to get in with the corporations.
‎ナイトシティで上に行くには
‎コーポに入り込むのがすべてだ
I'll require your continued assistance.
‎このまま君にも協力してもらおう
Gonna make me keep digging
this hole deeper?
‎（キーウィ）
‎これ以上 まだ裏切れっての？
‎（ファラデー）
‎いいチャンスだと思わないかね？
This is a great opportunity
for you as well.
I have corporate amnesty for
the Tanaka incident… But what about you?
‎私にはタナカ殺しの恩赦があるが
‎君はどうかな？
You're as slimy as ever.
‎（キーウィ）
‎汚い性格は相変わらずだね
Let's play nice for old time's sake.
‎（ファラデー）
‎昔のように仲よくしようじゃないか
How often do we get to work with Arasaka
and stick it to Militech with one hand?
‎アラサカの望みもかなえ
‎なおかつ ミリテクにも
‎一泡吹かせられる計画だ
Arasaka wouldn't object.
‎アラサカは きっと乗ってくる
I'll negotiate for your immunity
and commission.
‎君の免責と報酬も掛け合ってやろう
‎（キーウィ）‎ナイトシティでは
‎他人を利用するのが当たり前
Never trust a soul in Night City.
Trusting fools deserve
the hand they're dealt…
‎（キーウィ）‎利用されるほうが悪い
Is David a bargaining chip as well?
‎（キーウィ）‎デイビッドのことも
‎報告するつもり？
Naturally. I've conjured a plan.
‎（ファラデー）‎無論だ
‎それについてのいいプランも考えた
‎併せてアラサカに提案するつもりだ
I'll pitch them both to Arasaka.
‎（ホロコール着信音）
‎（ファラデー）
‎私だ　大きな仕事を頼みたい
What's up with the emergency meeting?
‎（レベッカ）
‎ずいぶん急な招集じゃん
Faraday's come through.
It's our biggest gig yet.
‎（デイビッド）
‎ファラデーから指名があった
‎今までにない でかい仕事だ
Huge risk, huge return. Turn back now
if you're not ready to face the heat.
‎リターンは大きいがリスクもでかい
‎もし抜けるやつがいたら言ってくれ
‎（ファルコ）ん？
‎（レベッカ）フッ
‎（デイビッド）フフッ
I'm counting on you too, Kiwi.
‎キーウィも よろしく頼むよ
Sure.
‎（キーウィ）ええ
‎（レベッカ）おい
Yo, granny and gramps
can bench this round.
‎おっさん オバサンは
‎無理しなくていいんだぜ～？
Think your little chicken legs'll
reach the pedals?
‎（ファルコ）
‎エスコートが必要だろ お嬢ちゃん
Kiss my ass.
‎（レベッカ）‎ブッころ！
Give us the brief.
‎（ファルコ）‎で 内容は？
'Saka put on a small,
heavy-duty security squad.
‎（デイビッド）
‎警備は少数精鋭　だが半分は——
But they'll split. Half'll go after
a diversion squad commissioned by Faraday.
‎ファラデーが仕込んだ陽動部隊が
‎引き剥がしてくれるはずだ
‎（アニマルズたちの笑い声）
Diversion squad?
‎（レベッカ）‎陽動部隊？
‎（キーウィ）
‎つまり おとりでしょ？
A decoy, basically. Though that's probably
not in the brief Faraday gave them.
‎自分たちが おとりとは
‎知らされてないでしょうけど
Oh.
‎（レベッカ）‎ああ～
Typical Faraday handiwork.
‎（ファルコ）
‎ファラデーがやりそうな手口だ
Of course, there's no way to tell
if we're also a decoy…
‎もっとも 俺たちも
‎おとりかもしれねえけどな
‎（発砲音）
Bitch!
‎（アニマルズ）この野郎！
‎（アニマルズ）ヘヘヘッ
‎おりゃー！
‎（アニマルズたちの叫び声）
‎（ファルコ）敵さん
‎うまいこと‎３：２(さんに)‎に分かれたぞ
Good, good. We've got 'em
nice and split. What's the call?
‎どうする！
Main target's off the road.
We've got the high ground.
‎（キーウィ）メインターゲットも
‎道をそれた　こっちが有利よ
Put her in gear, Falco!
‎よし　出せ ファルコ
Alright!
‎（ファルコ）オーライ
‎（レベッカ）そうこなくっちゃ
Let's hit it!
Hey, David. Car's all warmed and ready…
‎（レベッカ）おーい デイビッド
‎もう車の準備できてっぞ…
（倒れる音）
‎デイビッド！
David!
Are these all immunosuppressants?
‎お前 これ… 抑制剤か？
Can you fetch my mom's jacket for me?
‎あ… ああ
‎母さんの上着を取ってくれないか
We're calling off the gig!
‎（レベッカ）
‎仕事は中止だ　ドクんとこへ…
Rebecca… I got a favor to ask…
‎（デイビッド）
‎レベッカ… 頼みがあるんだ…
You better knock it--
‎（レベッカ）お前 いいかげんに…
‎（デイビッド）レベッカ！
Becca, I can't ask anyone else…
‎お前にしか 頼めないんだ…
‎ハア ハア ハア…
‎え…
‎んんん…
‎ん？　レベッカ？
Rebecca?
Puppy-dog eyes! Knew I'm
a sucker for the vulnerable, didn't ya?!
‎あーあ　いつからそんな
‎ズリい男になりやがったんだ！
Don't use your fucking Sandevistan.
You hear me?
‎いいか　サンデヴィスタンは
‎使うんじゃねえぞ！
Okay, okay…
‎（デイビッド）分かってるよ
‎イ～ッヒヒヒヒヒ！
‎（レベッカ）おらあーっ！
‎ヒューッ！　いっちょ上がり！
One down!
Alright, we're right on the target's ass!
‎（ファルコ）よっしゃ
‎ターゲットの後ろに張り付いた
I'll hack into the brake.
‎（キーウィ）ハックして停止させる
Hold on, we got a tail!
‎（ファルコ）
‎待て １台後ろに回ったぞ！
‎（レベッカ）うっ わっ！
Can't even get a peek out there!
‎弾幕が厚くて頭が出せねえ
Leave it to me!
‎俺に任せろ
Hey! Don't use your Sandevistan…
‎おい サンデヴィスタンは使う…
‎なー！
‎護衛車は制圧した
Fucking deaf, that one?!
‎使ってるよ～
‎フッハハ
‎（デイビッド）
‎このままターゲットに突っ込む
‎レベッカ
‎コンテナに地雷を投げろ！
You're a real piece of work!
‎ほんっと イカれてやがんぜっ！
‎うちのリーダーはよおおー！
Damn you, David!
‎（ガタン！）
‎（ファルコ）う… 無事のようだな
Everyone good?
‎おい ヒゲ　どういう目してんだ
Hey 'stache! Do we look good?!
Look.
‎（キーウィ）前見て
It's still going?!
‎（ファルコ）なんて装甲だ
ICE is as thick as the armor.
Can't hack it.
‎（キーウィ）
‎ＩＣＥも分厚い　ハックできない
Then I'll hit 'em from the front.
‎なら じかに前を潰す！
Seriously, knock it--
‎お前 いいかげんに…
‎っちったー
‎あたしの言うことも聞けって！
Fucking tired of being ignored!
‎あ！
‎（デイビッド）
‎運転手が乗ってない
‎何！
‎（デイビッド）
‎こいつ 無人運転だ
…on autopilot!
‎（ファラデー）
‎予定どおり 襲撃は進行中だ
‎やつらは期待どおりに
‎動いてくれている
‎（ケイト）
‎すばらしい働きだよ ファラデー
‎（ダグラス）‎万事順調というわけか
‎（ファラデー）
‎ミリテクにも すでにリーク済みだ
‎これでサイバースケルトンの
‎実戦データも手に入る
‎もっとも デイビッドが
‎サイバースケルトンに
‎適応したらの話だがな
‎（ケイト）
‎彼が それなりに働いてくれないと
‎私たちの回収部隊は
‎無傷のミリテクの部隊と
‎戦うはめになる
‎うまく潰し合ってくれないとな
‎（ファラデー）‎安心しろ
‎すべての駒は
‎私の思いどおりに進んでいる
So please.
Sit back, relax, and enjoy the show.
‎君らは安全な所から
‎眺めているだけでいい
‎（車の走行音）
Not good.
‎（キーウィ）マズい
‎早く止めないと崖に突っ込むよ
-We'd better stop it fast before it falls.
-What?!
‎（ファルコ）何！
‎（ホロ通信：レベッカ）
‎デイビッド！
‎（デイビッド）‎ああ 聞こえてる
‎（レベッカ）
‎離脱しろ　仕事は中止だ！
Alright… What are ya gonna do, David?
‎さあ
‎どうする？　デイビッド
We're right on the edge…
‎崖っぷちってやつだぞ
Falco! Pull up closer!
‎ファルコ　もっと寄せろ！
Easier said than done…
‎って言ったってよお！
‎（デイビッド）
‎ハープーンガンをこっちに射出しろ
‎何！
（デイビッド）
合図したら急ブレーキだ
（キーウィ）何する気？
（デイビッド）早くしろ
What do we do?!
‎どうする　どうする！
‎チッ　あたしが押してやるよ！
I'll shoot it if you won't!
That's right. Easy does it, David.
‎そうだ
‎しっかりしろ デイビッド
No one here to slap sense into you now.
‎まーた 引っぱたかれて
‎逃げ出す気か デイビッド
Make a choice.
‎自分で選択しろ
You're special, remember?
‎お前は——
‎特別なんだろ？
‎ぐーっ！
Brake!
‎ブレーキ！
‎踏め！
Slam on 'em!
‎おおおー！
‎（レベッカ）ハハハッ やったな
No way.
Th-That's how it's done.
‎（ファルコ）お… おうよ
‎（キーウィ）舌かんだわ
Bit my tongue…
‎フフッ
‎フンッ こいつはいい
How nice.
They send an executive-class AV
to collect a street girl?
‎たかが女一人の迎えに
‎コーポ専用の‎ＡＶ(エーブイ)‎をよこすとは
You really must be
their precious, lost toy.
‎カネのかかる女だ
‎（ホロコール発信音）
Still no response from Lucy?
‎どうだ　やっぱりルーシーは
‎出ないのか？
Ugh. What's one more runner
gonna do for us at this point?
‎んだよ
‎今さらランナーが増えても
‎やることねえだろ
‎大体 分け前が減るっての
You gonna pay her from your pot?
How's it going over there?
‎そっちはどうだ
Few more minutes to break the lock.
‎（キーウィ）
‎開錠には時間かかるかも
Is it just me or does it bother you
that this carrier was unmanned?
‎（ファルコ）しかしよ
‎こいつ無人だったの引っかかるよな
You sure it's an Arasaka vehicle?
‎ホントにアラサカなのか？
If you're so worried,
just take the cargo and go.
‎（キーウィ）不安なら さっさと
‎荷物 頂いてズラかるに限るね
We're all waiting on you.
‎なら さっさと開けてくれよ
Quit the yapping and let's go get our car.
‎グダグダ言ってねえで
‎今のうちに装甲車 取ってこようぜ
Sheesh. Didn't strike me back when
we were going after the carrier,
‎（ファルコ）うわ… さっきは
‎襲撃する側だったからよかったが
but we'd be fishes in a barrel
if anyone tried to shoot us out here.
‎こう隠れるものが
‎何もない荒野で襲われたら
‎ひとたまりもないな
Jesus, old man. Nervous fart like you
doesn't deserve that cowboy 'stache!
‎（レベッカ）さっきから
‎いちいちブルってんじゃねえよ
‎男らしいのは そのヒゲだけか～？
You'd go weak in the knees if I shaved.
‎（ファルコ）
‎俺がヒゲそったら ホレちまうぜ？
‎（レベッカ）うっせえ アホたれ！
Ew! Gonna kick it off!
‎うわっ　よけんな おい
Stop dodging, old man!
‎ふざけんなよ おい ジジイ！
‎（ファルコ）チッ
Looks like the decoy failed.
We've got company!
‎陽動で引き離したやつらが
‎戻ってきやがった
‎（爆発音）
What?!
‎（ファルコ）何ー！
‎（爆発音）
That a Basilisk?
‎（ファルコ）
‎バシリスク！　ミサイル車？
And a missile carrier!
You're shitting me…
‎（レベッカ）あいつらって
Militech!
‎ミリテクか！
‎いいっ！
‎（レベッカ･ファルコ）
‎うぐぐぐっ…
What the fuck?!
Why're we being steamrolled by Militech?!
‎どうなってんだ！
‎なんでミリテクに
‎こんな食らわされなきゃ…
‎（銃声）
Faraday's a Militech-man, ain't he?
‎ファラデーの雇い主は
‎ミリテクじゃなかったか？
‎いよいよ おかしなことに
‎なってきたぞ
The fishiness is really starting to reek!
‎（キーウィ）開いたー
‎（レベッカ）えっ 早っ！
It's open!
That was quick!
Take cover inside. Hurry!
‎（キーウィ）
‎ここじゃ‎殺(や)‎られる　とにかく中へ
What in the seven hells is this…?
‎（ファルコ）何なんだ こりゃ？
‎（デイビッド）これがファラデーが
‎メインに探させていたブツなのか？
This is what Faraday paid Maine to find?
So what is it?
‎それって結局 何だったわけ？
A cyberskeleton. Military implant.
‎（キーウィ）サイバースケルトン
‎軍事用インプラントよ
‎（レベッカ）軍事用って…
Military…
You mean like David's Sandevistan?
‎デイビッドのサンデヴィスタン
‎みたいなのってこと？
From what I hear,
it's a whole different caliber.
‎（キーウィ）サンデヴィスタンより
‎段違いにヤバいみたいよ
‎おいおい
Hey. This kid's Sandy ain't
nothing to turn your nose up at either.
‎こいつのサンデヴィスタンだって
‎相当なもんだぜ
First time I'm hearing about this.
‎（デイビッド）
‎そんな情報 俺は聞いてない
‎（キーウィ）真偽は不明
Believe me or don't.
Arasaka thinks they can overtake Militech
if this thing hits the market.
‎これが実用化されれば
‎軍事産業の面でアラサカが
‎ミリテクを‎凌駕(りょうが)‎できるって
‎ウワサされてるそうよ
‎ただ——
But they've kept its development
on the down-low.
‎このサイバースケルトンに関しては
‎アラサカの機密ぶりが徹底してて
Most of its information
was concentrated under Tanaka's wing.
‎タナカに情報を
‎集約し過ぎてたみたい
I don't know how,
but Faraday got wind of this,
‎どんなルートか知らないけど
‎ファラデーが これを嗅ぎつけ
‎ミリテクへリークすることで
‎都合のいい契約を結んでたみたいね
and promised to leak this tech to
Militech to get himself a nice deal.
‎ミリテクへリークすることで
‎都合のいい契約を結んでたみたいね
（ファラデー）
ハッハッハッハ
Not every day you get to fly
above Night City at your leisure.
‎ナイトシティを
‎自由に飛べるというのは
‎格別だな
‎君も冷たい氷風呂の中で
It must be a nice change of scenery
from your usual ice-filled baths.
‎ネットに溺れているだけでは
‎つまらなかろう
‎せっかくだから 彼が飛ぶのを
‎手伝ってあげようじゃないか
What do you say?
Want to help me make your boy fly?
（ホロコール着信音）
‎あ…
What?
（ホロコール着信音）
‎（ファルコ）どうした？
Incoming call from Lucy.
（ホロコール着信音）
‎ルーシーからコールだ
Now is seriously not the time!
‎（レベッカ）
‎はあ？　今 そんな場合じゃ…
‎（ルーシー）‎デイビッド
‎ルーシー　今までどこに…
‎（ルーシー）‎サイバースケルトンを
‎インストールして
‎はあ？
No time. Militech's coming.
‎（ルーシー）
‎時間がないの　ミリテクが迫ってる
How do you know that? Where are you?
‎（デイビッド）‎なぜ それを…
‎あ いや それより君は？
They're after me too.
‎（ルーシー）‎私も追われてる
‎何！
‎（ルーシー）
‎このままじゃ みんな死ぬわ
‎クッ…
‎（ルーシー）‎生き延びるなら
‎サイバースケルトンを
‎インストールして
‎急いで デイビッド
‎間に合わなくなる
‎（デイビッド）‎ルーシー 俺…
‎（ルーシー）
‎デイビッド あなたならできるわ
‎（通信切断音）
Lucy!
‎ルーシー！
What did she say?
‎（ファルコ）何だって？
‎（デイビッド）生き延びるなら
"Use the cyberskeleton
if you want to survive."
‎サイバースケルトンを
‎インストールしろって
The fuck?
‎はあ？
She didn't seem herself though.
‎（デイビッド）
‎でもルーシーらしくない
Sure about that?
‎知らねえよ
‎（デイビッド）
‎ルーシーも追われてるらしい
Someone's after her too.
I've gotta install it.
‎どちらにしても
‎俺がインストールするしかない
Whole truck's a mobile installation unit.
‎（キーウィ）このコンテナ自体が
‎インストールキットになってる
That deck's got the installer all set up.
‎そのデッキにインストーラーも
‎セッティング済み
You are not gonna install this thing!
‎まさか インストールする
‎つもりじゃねえよな？
I gotta get us out of this!
‎（デイビッド）
‎とにかく ここを切り抜ける
Are you insane?! You don't even know
what this hunk of metal can do!
‎答えになってねえ！
‎そんなものインストール
‎するなっつってんだよ！
I don't see any other option.
‎（デイビッド）このままでも
‎全員 殺されて終わりだ
Besides me knocking you the fuck out?!
‎（レベッカ）
‎お前 そろそろブン殴んぞ
I'm gonna go get our car.
‎（キーウィ）
‎私は装甲車を何とかする
I'll go with.
‎俺も行く
‎頼む
Thanks!
Last time I installed something that
wasn't mine, Maine beat the shit outta me.
‎前も売りもん
‎勝手にインストールして
‎メインに殴られたな
Some things just don't change!
‎何も変わっちゃいねえ
‎よせって
‎待て待て待て待て待て！
Don't! Wait…
‎あああーっ！
You fucking gonk!
Why don't you ever listen?!
‎入れちまったよ バカが！
‎（デイビッド）
‎ぐっ… あああああーっ！
What's Militech waiting for?
‎ミリテクのやつら
‎なぜ撃ってこねえ？
‎おい キーウィ
Kiwi, you able to get eyes on…
‎やつら… うっ
‎（キーウィ）悪いね
Sorry.
‎（ホロ通信：キーウィ）
‎お膳立てはしたわ　私は離脱する
‎よくやった　ミリテクにも
‎見逃すよう手配済みだ
‎例の場所で落ち合おう
‎何！
What?!
‎デイビッド！
‎ル… ルーシー？
‎（ルーシー）‎デイビッド
‎サイバースケルトンは
‎インストールしないで　ワナよ！
‎ルーシー 何があった？
‎君は無事か？
‎（ルーシー）‎ファラデーよ
‎全部 あいつが仕組んだ
‎（デイビッド）‎ファラデーが？
‎（ルーシー）
‎ファラデーはアラサカ側についた
‎あなたにサイバースケルトンを
‎インストールさせようとしてる
‎（デイビッド）
‎俺に？　何のために？
（ルーシー）
あなたとミリテクを
戦わせるつもりよ
‎そのあとで
‎アラサカの回収部隊が来る
‎全部 ワナなの！
‎サイバースケルトンを
‎インストールしちゃダメ
‎うっ
Did you truly think
we would put no failsafe in place?
‎（ファラデー）捕らえた時に
‎仕掛けぐらいしておくさ
‎（デイビッド）
‎ルーシー 何があった　ルーシー？
‎（ルーシー）
‎ミリテクが欲しがってるのは
‎サイバースケルトン
‎それを置いて… 逃げて
‎（デイビッド）
‎ルーシー！　ルーシー！
Shall I open a second neural port
in the back of your skull?
‎（ファラデー）
‎次はディープダイブ用の穴を
‎２つにしてやる
‎ルーシー！　どうしたんだ！
-I'm afraid she's currently indisposed.
-Faraday?!
‎彼女なら お休み中だ
‎ファラデー！
I trust the job is going well?
‎仕事は うまくいってるかね？
Fuck you, put Lucy back on!
‎ふざけやがって
‎ルーシーはどうした！
This chairjock bitch should feel grateful
to be kissing the ground.
‎仲間殺しの‎売女(ばいた)‎は
‎私の足元で地面と‎接吻(せっぷん)‎中だ
I was worried I might've
overscrambled her brain.
‎さんざん脳みそを
‎しゃぶってやったのに
‎まだイキ足りないようだ
Take your fucking foot off her!
‎足をどけろ ゲス野郎！
Don't be so serious.
I'm just having a ball of a time.
（ノイズ音）
‎（ファラデー）‎この売女は
‎アラサカが高値で買うそうだ
Besides, I won't have to lift a finger
when Arasaka's done with her.
‎これから届けに行く
‎あとは彼らがシャブってくれるさ
Faraday!
（警告音）
‎ファラデー！
‎サイバーサイコ化が早い
You're rapidly degenerating!
‎このままじゃインストール前に
‎イカれちまうぞ
At this rate, you're gonna
go psycho in seconds!
‎（ファラデー）
‎今 お前たちに迫っているのは
Elite Militech forces are closing in.
‎ミリテクの精鋭部隊だ
‎サイバースケルトンを
‎インストールして
Install the soft, use the cyberskeleton,
David. Lead your crew to safety.
‎その場を切り抜けてみせろ
‎君が それに耐えられるとは
‎到底 思えないが
Personally, I think it's beyond you.
Clearly Arasaka sees something I don't.
‎アラサカは期待しているようだ
‎自分が特別な存在だというなら
If you're truly so special, boy,
show me what you can do. Survive.
‎生き延びてみせろ 小僧
今すぐブッ殺してやる！
‎殺す 殺す 殺す…
I'll kill him! I'm gonna go kill him!
‎ブッ殺してやるっ！
‎殺す 殺す…
I'll kill him! I'll kill him…
‎ブッ殺す！
I'm gonna fucking--
‎ブッ殺してやるー！
‎（注入音）
You okay?
‎大丈夫か？
I'm gonna go save Lucy.
‎ルーシーを助けに行く
Uhh… Nope, I think your brain's fried.
‎はあ？
‎やっぱりイカれちまったか？
Faraday's double-crossed us.
He's got Lucy.
‎ファラデーが裏切りやがった
‎ルーシーも捕まってるんだ
Huh? What do you mean?
‎何？　どういうこと？
‎ダマしやがって
‎絶対に許さねえ！
That fucker.
I'm gonna fucking put him in the ground!
I swear, he's gonna fucking die…
‎必ずブッ殺してやる！
David…
‎お前…
Falco! What happened?
‎ファルコ　どした？
Kiwi got me.
‎（ファルコ）キーウィにやられた
What?!
‎ああ？
She led us into a trap.
‎俺たち ハメられたんだ
Oh, that hag. She's in it too?
‎（レベッカ）
‎あのクソババアもグルか！
She's a fucking flatline
when I see her next!
‎ぜってえ生かしちゃおかねえ！
‎（レベッカ）
‎うおおっ また始まったぞ
Here we go again!
Shit!
‎ヤバい ヤバい
‎ミリテクのやつら めちゃくちゃだ
Militech's really out to kill us!
I've never seen anything like this.
‎（キーウィ）‎とんでもなく
‎ヤバい代物だよ これは
How can anyone walk with this on?
‎（ファルコ）
‎こんなの自重で立てないだろ
‎（キーウィ）‎エアロビークルに
‎搭載されてるジェットエンジンを
Two compact thrusters're built in.
Same kind you get on an AV.
‎小型化したものが２機
‎そして何より
On top of that, Arasaka engineered in
a gravity modification prototype.
‎アラサカが編み出した
‎反重力テクノロジーが使われてる
‎（兵士）あ… うわっ
It can generate unidirectional
grav fields, magnetic forces, too…
‎（キーウィ）‎ポイントは
‎指向性の重力場と磁力発生装置ね
That's the magnetic force generator?
‎あれが磁力発生装置か
Hot damn!
He just mowed a small squad down!
‎おいおい　一瞬で すげえ‎殺(や)‎ったぞ
He's using his Sandevistan, too.
‎あいつ サンデヴィスタンも
‎使ってやがる
‎（兵士）うおっ！
‎あっ！
He's flying!
‎浮いてる
That's the gravitational field?
‎（ファルコ）重力場ってやつか
‎（２人）あ…
But this tech hasn't left
its testing stage.
‎（キーウィ）‎ただ 完全に実験段階
The controls are too complex.
‎制御が複雑すぎて
‎何しろ搭乗者の五感 全神経が
There's no guarantee that the equipper's
nerves will be able to withstand it.
‎耐えられる保証がない
It requires an insane level
of mental fortitude against implants.
‎インプラントへの耐性が
‎異常なまでに求められる
A one-way ticket to
cyberpsychosis, you mean.
‎（ファルコ）
‎つけたら一発でサイバーサイコだな
They got him?!
‎やられちまった！
‎（レベッカ）デイビッド
David…
‎（デイビッドのうなり声）
He's still going!
‎無事だったか
‎（レベッカ）体が無事でも…
His body is, but…
‎（キーウィ）
‎使えば使うほど人間性コストを失い
The more he uses it, the closer he will be
to overloading his cyberware capacity.
‎クロームと同化し
‎精神と引き換えに得られる戦闘力
But in exchange, the short-term
power it generates is…
‎（２人）あ…
unlike anything devised
on this side of sanity.
‎（キーウィ）
‎まさにエッジの向こう側ね
‎（ノック音）
‎（２人）ん？
David?
‎（レベッカ）デイビッド？
We're going after Faraday
for betraying us.
‎（デイビッド）俺たちをハメた
‎ファラデーをブッ殺して
‎ルーシーを助ける
And we're gonna save Lucy.
You say that but…
‎っつったって…
Equal share of the pot.
‎（デイビッド）
‎分け前はフェアにやる
‎（２人）ん？
That's my style.
‎それが俺の流儀だ
‎（２人）フッフフフ
Alright, buddy.
‎つきあってやるよ
Onwards to hell.
‎地獄までな
♪～
～♪